Sae Pak

Front-end Developer

Info

- [] (236) 986-2247
- in linkedin.com/in/sae-pak
- www.sae-pak.com
- https://github.com/saepak

Technical Skills

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, NPM, React.js, Wordpress, GraphQL, jQuery

Tools

Visual Studio Code, Git, Android Studio, Xcode

Other

UI framework, Trello, Slack, MS office

Projects

Kovan

: A management solution. React-Native, Native-Base, React-Hooks, SVG

Movie Box

: A quick movie finder. React, Material-UI, TMDB API

My Expense Manager

: An expense tracker. React-Hooks, Chart.js, Google OAuth, Ant design

Image Gallery

: A high quality image library. React-Hooks, Pixabay API, Tailwind CSS

Profile

A self-motivated professional with extensive team collaboration involvement. 3+ years experience building websites and web applications for a multitude of clients.

Teamwork skills / Detail-oriented / Time management / Understanding of UX design / Problem solving

Professional Experience

Emeye (Seoul, South Korea) / UI developer

Dec 2015 - Dec 2017

- Built websites and web apps using HTML5, CSS3 and jQuery.
- Worked on a variety of clients and project types.
- Validated CSS style sheet using W3C Validation Service for error-free performances.
- Worked on websites maintenance including correcting issues and making updates to ensure that client's websites are running at full capacity.

Results: Experienced many different types of user interfaces including responsive design. Learned how to multitask and manage time efficiently.

Konest (Seoul, South Korea) / UI developer

Mar 2014 - May 2015

- Changed the website code from HTML3 to HTML5 / CSS3 and made it responsive.
- Collaborated with content managers and web designers to create web pages for the up-to-date information delivery.
- Updated the website to make it easier to use and navigate.
- Worked with clients to create customized landing pages for their marketing campaign.

Results: Learned the foundations of markup languages. Developed collaboration skills with marketing, content, design and development teams to achieve the same goals.

Education

Langara college (Vancouver, Canada)

May 2019 - Dec 2020

Post-Degree Diploma / Dean's Honour Roll.
Web and Mobile App Design and Development.